

Syed Muhammad **Saglain**

Contact

- +92 300 0580479
- saqlainprinters @gmail.com
- @saqlain1020
- in @saqlain1020
- (#) https://saqlain1020.com

Skills

Frontend:

Backend:

Blockchain:

Devops:

Heroku (Mercel) *Turborepo *Firebose
*Railway) *AWS Beanstolik *AWS Pipeling
*AWS Amplify *AWS Codebuild *AWS EC2
*AWS RouteS3 *AWS Cortificate Manager
*AWS Cloudfront) *AWS S3 *Netlify
*AWS S3 *Netlify
*AWS Cloudfront) *AWS Cl

Others:

• Java • C# • MySql • Jira • Trello

Java C MySql Jira Trello
 Discord Bot Photoshop Illustrator
 Domain Mangement Asana

About me

I'm Saqlain an ambitious problem solver with a passion for learning and implementing new solutions, and who would like to join a team of like-minded developers. Experienced in creating logical and innovative solutions of complex problems.

My goal is to climb the ladder and become one of the leading experts in my field, and want to be a part of something bigger.

Education

2019-Current

BS:SE University of Karachi

2018

Intermediate Adamjee Govt Science College

Matriculation

Work Experience

2021 - Current

Dechains

Role: Senior Frontend Developer, I am responsible for creating whole responsive frontend of various blockshain related apps illia NFT Marispiaces, Farming sites etc. While integrating and working on modularized custom libraries for apis, graph and blockshain communication, Libs being compiled with webpack; rollup, tsup etc

2020 - 2021

Slectus (US)

Multivendor ecommerce style platform with commission support and a complex profile and product management system and realtime features, MERN Stack App. Role: Frontend Developer, responsible for all the frontend work and integrations on the platform, little backend development authorized.

2020 - 2020

Novasoft

Software House.

Role: Frontend Developer, responsible for most of the frontend work and integrations on their multiple projects in works.

1 Year

Al-Raheem Printing Services

Role: Graphics Designer

3rd Party Projects

Some of many third party app i have developed as a developer

NFT-Crypto web apps on ReactJS | Apple Mapkit React App

Firebase Data and Auth applications Social Links sharing apps with NFC tag functionality

Many of my projects can be viewed on my webportfolio https://saqlain1020.com

Extras

Fiverr freelancing experience Certificates:-

- Webicamp module winner
- Graphics desiging from Arena Multimedia
- Contribution ICISCT 2020

Envoirment Modeling Workshop participation by Comstech of OIC